# **FUAIDIL IKHROM**

IT Enthusiast



# CONTACT

\_\_\_

### **ADDRESS**

Jl. Tlogo Sari No.37EE, Tlogomas, Kec. Lowokwaru, Kota Malang, Jawa Timur 65144

#### **PHONE**

(+62) 85975127759

#### **EMAIL**

ifuaidil@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

\_\_

- Java
- PHP
- HTML
- CSS
- Microsoft Office
- Dart
- Python

# **LANGUAGES**

\_\_\_

- English
- Arabic

#### **SUMMARY**

\_

Enthusiastic and highly motivated Informatics Engineering student with the ability to think critically, be optimistic, and look for new challenges. Experienced in campus organizations and able to adapt to a dynamic environment and be able to work with people from different backgrounds.

### **EDUCATION**

\_

# UNDERGRADUATE, UIN MAULANA MALIK IBRAHIM

Malang

July 2021 – Present Informatic Engineering

# HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, SMK N 2 Surakarta

Surakarta

July 2018 - Mei 2021 Software Engineering

#### **EXPERIENCE**

\_

# Intellectual Division Member, HIMATIF-Encoder

Malang

July 2022 – November 2022.

# **Staff, Weboender Community**

Malang

October 2022 – September 2023

# Member, Google Developer Student Club Community

Malang

October 2022 – Present

# **Leader, Weboender Community**

Malang

September 2023 – September 2024

# Backend Developer, PT. Dkenzi Wastu Baskara

Malang

April 2024 – July 2024

Internship

#### **PROJECTS**

\_

- Cellphone Store Sales Web-App
- Car Rental Web-App
- Outdoor Equipment Rental Web-App
- Hospital Information System (Web-Based)
- System Library App (Desktop-Based)
- Travel App (Mobile-Based)
- Hand Gesture Robot